Okay, the other function that's really
helpful to know um is the set interval.
So the set interval um to have that run,
I'm just going to change this log
statement slightly so you can see a
little bit of the difference. I'm going
to create a global variable here. I'm
going to say let counter or let seconds
equal zero. And then here in this log,
I'm just going to log out. Um,
sorry.
Waited for
seconds.
seconds seconds. So, I'm going to log
out however many seconds it's been, and
I'm going to increment seconds before I
log it. Okay. Now, I'm going to adjust
this slightly. The main difference
between set interval and set timeout is
the way you define them. So this one I
just say set interval. Then I give it a
function that I want it to run and I
give it a pause time. In this case I'm
going to put 1,000 milliseconds so that
we get every second. So now if I save
this and I come over to my workspace,
you can see that every second it logs
out exactly how long it waited for. And
so with this we can track the passage of
time. And with set timeout, we can have
things pause. Having things pause will
simulate making requests out to the
internet. And this interval here will
tell us exactly how long we've been
waiting.